First, unzip the downloaded zip file and open the .blend file
You will see rigs and models like this one
The collections in the left outline contain the models reguired'foreachControlNet.
The collections inthe left outline contain the models reguiredforeachControlNet.
The collectionsinthe left outliner contain the models reguiredforeachControlNet n
The collectionsinthe left outliner contain the models reguiredforeachControlNet.
The collections in the left outliner contain the models reguiredforeachControlNet.
The collections in the left outliner contain the models reguiredforeachControlNet
The collections in the left outliner contain the models reguiredfor each ControlNet
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Praeh To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Trackba To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Trah To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Trackba To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
a Now you can adjust the pose Resete Mod Stan
Now you can adjust the pose g c ResetAllPo a
Now you can adjust the pose A ResetAllPo ka a
Now you can adjust the pose Pick E ReetAllPoe a
Now you can adjust the pose Convertor Now you can adjust the pose 公 Convertor
Now you can adjust the pose k Reet
Now you can adjust the pose k ReetAllPou
Now you can adjust the pose 生工 Pick ReetAllPou
Now you can adjust the pose 生工 Pick ReetAlPo a
Now you can adjust the pose Stan
Now you can adjust the pose KHAIE ar i ResetAlPo a
Now you can adjust the pose KHAI g k ResetAlPo
Now you can adjust the pose AI二 g k ResetAlPo o a
Now you can adjust the pose A k E ResetAlPo o a
Tracibad Now you can adjust the pose ar Pick ReetAlPoe a
Now you can adjust the pose
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloadedfile intovour-blenderaddon
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the downloaded'file into vourblenderaddon
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloadedfileintoyourblenderaddon
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the downloadedfileintoyourblenderaddon
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the downloaded file into vourblenderaddon
So KHAIH RetAlPoe >
@ Stan ResetAllPoy o
K Stan
Tracibal Stan
o @ E
A ao @ Stan e
stan
AI sar
AI
HHAIHH
HHAIHH ?
HHAINH Stan
A 会
HHAINH g
· HHAIH
HHAIH ?
HHAIH
HHAINH g
HHAINH $ e
Trackball HHAINH g
Trackbad HHAIHH g g
HHAIHH g g
ta HHAIHH g g
HHAIHH @
Now let's adjust the camera Stan ar
Now let's adjust the camera Stan Sar
Now let's adjust the camera Stan a
Now let's adjust the camera HHAIM Stan E a
Now let's adjust the camera HAI Stan E a
Now let's adjust the camera A 南 Stan a
Now let's adjust the camera Stan Sar
When you have the right pose and camera, hit the render button
After rendering, a new folder is created in the path of the blendfile.button
In the folder, images for each controlnet are saved
First, let's use an openpose_full
and Fll thisControlNetunit First, let's use an openpose full
First, let's use an openpose full Save zip Send to Send to
ackgroundandblacklines AllowPreviev First, let's use an .openpose_full imgimg inpaint
ackgroundandblacklines AllowPreview First, let's use an openpose futl ConfigPresets Sendto imgimg Sendto inpaint
tackgroundandblacklines, AllowPreview First, let's use an openpose fut ConfigPresets Sendto imgimg Sendto inpaint
tackgroundandblacklines, AllowPreview First, let's use an openpose fut ConfigPresets Sendto imgimg Send to inpaint
ackground and black lines, AllowPreview First,let'suseanopenposefutl Sendto imgimg miebqualitygiobondhiluluwhitdssa Ngativom:(wquality,wquality),bur,uryhff Step. nlerDPM++MKarrasCEGee oedSize-x Sendto inpaint
ackgroundandblacklines AllowPreview First,let'susean.openposefull imgimg drssnai urry.depthoffield ublurbhu inpaint StepsSampler:DPM++M Karras,CFG scaleSeedSize:x,Modelhash:fbe,Model:llustration_Coun preprocessor.none odetcontrolvipsdiop enpoecabdl mode:CropandResize, ().esze
ackground and black lines AllowPreview Savt ZP imgimg masterpiece,bestquality,girf,solo,blondehair,blueeyes,bluesky,whitedress,ponytail Naimt:wstqualitowquality.),blurbluythffi inpaint Steps Sampler:DPM++M Karras,CFG scaleSeedSize:x,Model hash:fbe,Model:illustration_Coun"preprocessor:none,model:control_vp_sd_openpose[cabd],weightstarting/ending:(,),resizemode:Cropand Resize,
Once you'ye got the image you want, it's time to modify the hand. Save Zip Send to Send to
Once you've got the image you want, it's time to modify the hand.
Itis possibletocreate animage at oncewittrmultiple controlnetsbut prefertouseinpat
It is'possible to create an image at once with multiple controlnets,butprefertouseinpaint Send to Send to
Itispossibletocreateanimageat-oncewithmultiple StartingControlSten controlnets,butTpreferto useinpaint
Itispossibletocreateanimageatoncewithmultiple controlnets,butprefer.to use inpaint ra lnpaint globa
Itispossibletocreateanimageatoncewithmultiple controlnets.butTprefertousejnpaint Send to Send to
Itispossibletocreateanimageatoncewithmultiple controlnets.butTprefertouseinpaint Send to Send to
Itispossibletocreateanimageatoncewithmultiple ox量controlnets, but I prefer to use inpaint
eand Fill this Contre It is possible to createan imageat once with multiple controlnets, but I prefer to use inpaint
eand Fill this Contre It is possibleto createan imageat once with multiple controlnets, but I prefer to use inpaint
hisc It is possible to create an image at once with multiple controlnets, but I prefer to use inpaint
his c It is possible to create an image at once with multiple controlnets, but I prefer to use inpaint
This time we use the Line Art anime ControlNet to modify thehand.
This time we use the Line Art anime ControlNet to modify the hand.
hisc This time we use the Line Art anime ControlNet to modify the hand.
e and Fill thisControlNetunit And Inpainting ControlNet
And Inpainting ControlNet Save Zip Send to Send to
And Inpainting ControlNet Save Zip Send to Send to And Inpainting ControlNet Save Zip Send to Sendto
Now draw a mask on the hand on the image Save Zip Send to Send to
Now draw a mask on theHand on the image
Now draw a mask on theand on the ima
图
nothine Save Zip Sendto O Sendto nnn
nothing Save Zip Sendto O Sendto nnn
hothing Save Zip Sendto Sendto nnan
图
hothins Save Zip Send to Sendto nnn
Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
eand Fil this Control Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
eand Fil this Controll Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
and Fil his con Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
and F his con Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
hisControll Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
hiscontroll Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
and Fil this con Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
itrolNetUnit Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail ControlNetUnit
Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail Batche Save Zip Sendto Send to
Finally, use the tile control netito enhance the detail Batch
Finally, use the tile control netto enhance the detail
Finally, use the tile control netto enhance the detail Batch
Finally, use the tile control netlto enhance the detail Batch
Finally, use the tile control netito enhance the detail Batch
Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail Batchco Save Zip Sendto Sendto
Finally,use the tile control net to enhancetfe detail
Finally,use thetilecontrol net toenhaneethe detail
Finally, use the tile control net to enhance the detail
Small details like facial expressions require high enough resolution